Install icagenda 2.0
The version you have installed
Configuration of the calendar module
Select the position of the module iCcalendar
Publish module
Module Assignment to pages
Select 'Left' to display the tooltip to the left of the module,
'Right' to display the tooltip to the right of the module,
or select 'Middle of the page' to center the tip horizontally in the middle of your page
also indicate if you want to display at the top or bottom,
if Middle of the page selected
Select whether the tooltip should open on mouse over
or by clicking on the date of the calendar module
Indicate the date format, in tooltip
Now select the template (design of our calendar)
There are two theme packs included, but you can create and install others.
Select the first day of the week,
Sunday or Monday
We can indicate which category refers calendar.
Currently we have not created any category.
Save and close the module management
Have a look at your calendar module!
There is something not set!
Don't worry! You just need to create a menu
to be connected to iCagenda.
In menu manager, click on 'New'
Select iCagenda > list of events, in Menu Item Type
Add a title to this new menu link
Set which events you want to display,
all events, future or past events
You can choose to display only one category
Éselect order of the list
Select the theme for your events list
Éhow many characters in the short description!
Énumber of events per page
Édate format in event list, and details
you can add a personal separator for dates with numbersÉ
Width of the GoogleMap.
(useful for some template to select a 99%)
Height of the GoogleMap.
(in pixel)
Save and Close
Reload the page...
Excellent! Info message removed.
Click on the item menu...
Still a white page, but you need now to add events.
Tutorial to add events in the next video, part 2!