create categories
insert the name of the first category
...assign a color
click "save and new"
repeat the same steps for the second category
repeat the same operations for the third category (and so on!)
save and close
These newly created categories
create your first event
insert the name or title of the event
assign it to a category
check that the status is "published"
insert date and time of the event
insert start date and time of the event
expand the menu to read the detailed instructions on the use of multiple dates and times
insert image of the event
you can also attach a PDF file to download
insert the contact information for this event,
for example, the email address of the event organizer
Here we insert the location of the event
Here we can add the event information
(advice for SEO, enter an adequate description)
options for event registration
if you want to add sharing of the event on social networks, enable the display
(it's possible to select global options of the component)
Activate registration
for each event you can register by date, period
Insert the number of tickets / reservations available
Insert how many places available to each registration
Now insert the postal address of the event
starting to enter an address, Google Maps propose possible locations...
Here is our address!
enable satellite view
Move the marker to the center of the building
these are the GPS coordinates
this is our first event back-end
enter another event
Now enter an event that is repeated several times and for a period
(for example, the projection of a movie in a cinema)
insert the period in which the event takes place,
Insert start and end dates (date and time).
the event lasts a week....
now insert the various dates with the various times,
of the projection of the movie
enter the dates and times of all projections
now insert the movie poster
insert a brochure in pdf
Using API of Google Maps!
it seems that the movie theater is a field....
Move the marker to the appropriate location
insert the name of the cinema,
city ​​and country
...contact information
in the description insert the film's plot,
maybe without revealing the ending!
here not activate any type of registration
here are our two events
let's look at the front-end
Events entered appear immediately
in the tooltip, shows the day January 7
the layout of all events
let's look at the concert of Eros Ramazzotti and....
register for a booking
at the top left the number of places available (10000)
return back, to see the details of the concert...
places left are now 9998 (2 less)
we can download the concert program
navigate in the map
see if there are other concert dates
see a preview of the concert to be held by March...
view of the film program...
dates and showtimes....
the programming period....